cnbhomes.com 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy | Home Design Ideas

CNBhomes.com is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement applies to the data collected by CNBhomes.com through site it does not apply to data collected through other online or offline CNBhomes.com sites, products or services.

**Collection of Your Personal Information**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. The personal information we collect may include name, e-mail address, phone, postal address, zip code, and credit card number.

We may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with the Site. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses.

In order to offer you a more consistent and personalized experience in your interactions with CNBhomes.com, information collected through one CNBhomes.com service may be combined with information obtained through other CNBhomes.com services. We may also supplement the information we collect with information obtained from other companies. For example, we may use services from other companies that enable us to derive a general geographic area based on your IP address in order to customize certain services to your geographic area.

**Use of Your Personal Information**

The personal information collected on this Site will be used to operate the Site and to provide the service(s) or carry out the transaction(s) you have requested or authorized. In support of these uses, CNBhomes.com may use personal information to provide you with more effective customer service, to improve the Site and any related CNBhomes.com products or services, and to make the Site easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Site to your particular preference or interests.

We may use your personal information to provide you with important information about the product or service that you are using, including critical updates and notifications. Additionally, with your permission, we may send you information about other CNBhomes.com products and services, and/or share information with CNBhomes.com partners so they may send you information about their products and services.

CNBhomes.com occasionally hires other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as Web site hosting, packaging, mailing and delivering prizes, answering customer questions about products and services, and sending information about our products, special offers, and other new services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.

CNBhomes.com may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on CNBhomes.com or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of CNBhomes.com and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of CNBhomes.com products or members of the public.

Personal information collected on the Site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which CNBhomes.com or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. CNBhomes.com abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

**Control of Your Personal Information**

Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of CNBhomes.com and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your permission.

Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to CNBhomes.com in the context of other, separately operated, CNBhomes.com products or services.

**Use of Cookies**

We use cookies on this Site to ensure the integrity of the registration process and to personalize the Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of delivering relevant content, eases site navigation, and so on. When you return to the web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the site’s features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to use interactive features of this or other web sites that depend on cookies.

**Use of Web Beacons**

Pages on this Site may contain electronic images known as Web beacons – sometimes called single-pixel gifs – that may be used to assist in delivering cookies, to allow us to count users who have visited those pages, and to deliver co-branded services. We may also include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or our newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

CNBhomes.com may also employ Web beacons from third parties in order to help us compile aggregated statistics and determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns or other operations of our sites. We prohibit Web beacons on our sites from being used by third parties to collect or access your personal information. We may work with other companies that advertise on our sites to place Web beacons on their sites in order to allow us to develop statistics on how often clicking on an advertisement on a CNBhomes.com site results in a purchase or other action on the advertiser’s site.

**Advertising**

CNBhomes.com may display advertisements that are periodically updated. Advertisements in CNBhomes.com may be delivered by CNBhomes.com or by other companies (third-party ad networks or ad servers) that CNBhomes.com allows to display advertisements to you.

Information collected, processed or transmitted: CNBhomes.com and some of these ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement. Advertisements displayed in CNBhomes.com may contain electronic images known as Web beacons – sometimes called single-pixel gifs – in order to help compile aggregated statistics and determine the effectiveness of promotional campaigns. We prohibit Web beacons in advertisements displayed in CNBhomes.com from being used by third parties to collect or access your personal information. We may work with other companies that advertise in CNBhomes.com to place Web beacons on their sites in order to allow us to develop statistics on how often clicking on an advertisement in CNBhomes.com results in a purchase or other action on the advertiser’s site. In addition, advertisements may be stored on your machine for display while you are offline.

Use of information: CNBhomes.com and ad networks may compile information about what advertisements are seen in CNBhomes.com and determine which ads are clicked on. CNBhomes.com may also share this information with ad networks. This information allows CNBhomes.com and ad networks to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Choice/Control: This advertising functionality is required for the use of the product. If you do not want advertisements to display, or do not want to download cookies or web beacons, you can choose not to use this product.

**Special Note About Google Advertising**

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to [opt out of Google’s cookie usage](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

We may occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “Last Updated” date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this privacy statement, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our web site or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

**Contact Information**

CNBhomes.com welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement or believe that we have not adhered to it, please contact us.
